Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. (CSEA), American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Local 1000 Records apap015
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- CSEA 100 Project, 1998-2009; 9; 97 Digital Files
  - Video of interview with Lorraine Hickey-Korf, Undated
    Served as secretary for statewide treasurers Mary Sullivan and Maureen Malone.
  - Transcript of interview with Lorraine Hickey-Korf, Undated
  - Video of interview with Tom Hobart, 2004 December
    President of the New York State United Teachers Union.
  - Transcript of interview with Tom Hobart, 2004 December
  - Video of interview with Nancy Hoffman, 2006 June 21
    Former CSEA General Council speaking about her role with the CSEA.
  - Transcript of interview with Nancy Hoffman, 2006 June 21
  - Video of interview with Dennis Hughes, 2006 June 21
    AFL-ClO president speaking about CSEA.
  - Transcript of interview with Dennis Hughes, 2006 June 21
  - Video of interview with Jim Kelly, 2006 July 20
    Son of former CSEA lead council John Kelly speaking about his father.
  - Transcript of interview with Jim Kelly, 2006 July 20
  - Video of interview with Nick Lamorte, Undated
    Current CSEA president for the Long Island Region.
  - Transcript of interview with Nick Lamorte, Undated
  - Video of interview with Marty Langer, 2001 July
    Served as statewide political action chairman under Bill Mcgowan. Langer was director of the Labor Management Committee and went on to be the consultant for CSEA's Mental Hygiene Group.
  - Transcript of interview with Marty Langer, 2006 June 22
    Activist and unofficial CSEA historian speaking about the union.
  - Transcript of interview with Marty Langer, 2001 July
  - Transcript of interview with Bob Lattimer, 2001 July
    Served as president of the Buffalo City Local, 1970-1972. Held chair of the AFSCME Affiliation Committee. Served as the CSEA Region VI President for over 24 years.
  - Transcript of interview with Jermone "Jerry" Lefkowitz, 2001 July
    Served 19 years as deputy chairman of PERB. Also served as deputy counsel of CSEA.
  - Transcript of interview with Jerome Lefkowitz, 2005 April
    Speaking about the Taylor Law.
  - Transcript of interview with Bill Lochner, 2007 March 1
  - Video of interview with Bill Lochner, 2007 March 1
  - Transcript of interview with William Lucy, 2003 July
  - Transcript of interview with Stephen Madarasz, 2009 December 16
    Former director of communications (retired 2016) speaks about his experiences at CSEA.
  - Video of interview with H. Carl McCall, 2005 May
    Former New York State senator and comptroller speaking about his working relationship with CSEA.
  - Transcript of interview with H. Carl McCall, 2005 May
  - Transcript of interview with Joe McDermott, 2003 September
    Served as the Capital Region president (1973-1982), executive vice presdident (1982-1984), and statewide president (1988-1994).
  - Transcript of interview with Gerald McEntee, 2003 July
  - Transcript of interview with Joe McMullen, 2009 November 2
    Former statewide treasurer (retired 2016) speaking about the union.
  - Transcript of interview with Terry Melvin, 2009 November 2
  - Transcript of interview with Sam Mogavero, 2009 March 12
    CSEA retiree talking about his experiences with the union.
  - Transcript of interview with Elizabeth Moore, 2005 April
    Former assistant council for labor issues for Governors Hugh Carey and Mario Cuomo.
  - Transcript of interview with Jim Moore, 2007 April 24
  - Transcript of interview with Elaine Mootry, Undated
    Served on the State Board of Directors and as a CSEA delegate.
  - Transcript of interview with Mike Moran, 2003 July
    Twice held the post of director of communications for CSEA.
  - Transcript of interview with Michael Murphy, 2002 April
    Local president of Central Islip Psychitric Center from 1965-1973.
  - Transcript of interview with Mel Osterman, 2005 May
    Former New York State director of cmployee relations speaking about working with the CSEA.
  - Transcript of interview with Nick Palacino, Undated
    Held position of field representative for CSEA and serviced the psychiatric centers of Long Island.
  - Transcript of interview with Governer George Pataki, 2009 November 12
    Former New York State governor speaking about the Union.
  - Transcript of interview with Charlie Peritore, 2002 October
    Served as chair and president of Chapter 1000 of AFSCME.
  - Transcript of interview with Gary Perkinson, 2009 September 22
  - Transcript of interview with Joseph L. Persico, 2006 July 18
    Author and former speech writer for Governer Nelson Rockefeller speaking about his relationship with the CSEA.
  - Transcript of interview with Tom Quimby, 2004 December
    Former CSEA field representative, director of education and director of LEAP.
  - Transcript of interview with Joe Reedy, 2005 April
    Former CSEA collective bargaining specialist speaking about his career.
  - Transcript of interview with Jack Rice, 2005 April
    Speaking about various aspects of the Taylor Law.
  - Transcript of interview with Jack Rice, Undated
    Worked as a lawyer in the firm of Degraf, Foy, Connelly, and Holt Harris ( the counsel for CSEA Starting in the 1930s). Held position of principle partner in charge of CSEA from 1967-1972.
  - Transcript of interview with Judy Richards, 2005 April
    Former president of SUNY Empire State College Local CSEA.
  - Transcript of interview with Judy Richardson, 1998 September
    Served as director of insurance for CSEA starting in 1986.
  - Transcript of interview with James Roemer, 2003 April
    Attorney and former general counsel to CSEA.
  - Transcript of interview with Larry Scanlon, 2005 April
    AFSCME political director speaking about his various roles and jobs within the CSEA.
  - Transcript of interview with Rita Slattery, Undated
    Served as executive secretary to the vice president and assistant to the president. When interviewed she held the position of office manager/assistant to the president.
  - Transcript of interview with David Stack, 2006 June 22
    CSEA director of internal operations speaking about the union.
  - Transcript of interview with Gregory G. Szurmcki, 2003 April
    Helped organize a local at Kings Park Psychiatric Center. Served as local president and was co-author of first election manual for CSEA.
  - Transcript of interview with Flo Trippi, 2002 October
    Helped organize a Health Department unit of CSEA and served as president. Now serves as Region 6 president.
  - Transcript of interview with Rita Wallace, Undated
    Served as the third, second, and first executive vice president, and president of Nassau Local. At the time of the interview, was also serving on the Nassau University Medical Center Board of Directors following appointment by Governer Pataki.
  - Transcript of interview with Daniel Walsh, 2006 June 21
    Business Council of New York State president speaking about the CSEA.
  - Transcript of interview with Dr. Michael Wilkins, 2007 August 19
    Physcian who was instrumental in revealing the terrible conditions at the Willowbrook Hospital in the 1970s.
- Images, 1947-2013; 10; 2.8 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  This series contains prints, slides, and negatives. They include images of individuals, buildings, and events.
  - 255 Lark, Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 1)
  - AFSCME Gathering, Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 2)
  - AFSCME in the Public Service, 2002 June (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 3)
  - AFSCME Saves Harlem Hospital, Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 4)
  - Anti-Nafta CSEA Rally, 1993 (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 5)
  - Awards, 1963; Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors, 1984; 1990; Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors Candidates, 1978; 1983; 1986 (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors Elections; Statement and Photos, 1992-1993; 1995-1996 (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors; Special Elections, 1987-1990; 1993 (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 10)
  - Buildings (1 of 4), 1984; 1986-1992; 1994; Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 11)
  - Buildings (2 of 4), 1984; 1986-1992; 1994; Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 12)
  - Buildings (3 of 4), 1984; 1986-1992; 1994; Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 13)
  - Buildings (4 of 4), 1984; 1986-1992; 1994; Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 14)
  - Candidate Photos; Statewide Board of Directors, 1989; 1994 (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 15)
  - Carpet W.H. Price Slides, Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 16)
  - Clinton and Gore, 1996 (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 17)
  - Conference and Workshops, 1981; 1985; Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 18)
  - CSEA, 1986 (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 19)
  - CSEA Convention, Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 20)
  - CSEA-Dol- Delegation to D.C., 1987 Febuary (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 21)
  - CSEA - Joel and Rita Delegate Slides, Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 22)
  - CSEA for McCall, 2002 (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 23)
  - CSEA Media Picnic, Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 24)
  - CSEA Misc., 1980; Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 25)
  - CSEA and NCBI, 2010 (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 26)
  - CSEA Open House, 1986 (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 27)
  - Country Slideshows, Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 28)
  - Dan Campell - Delegate Slides, 1984 July (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 29)
  - D.C. Convention - CSEA Indoors, 1993 (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 30)
  - Delegate Slides, Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 31)
  - Dinners, 1971-1972; Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 32)
  - Educational - NEI, 1977; 1984; 1986-1989; 1991-1993; Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 33)
  - Educational Set, 1983-1991; 1994; 1996-1997; Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 34)
  - Elections/ Election Procedures, 1971 (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 35)
  - Farmingdale 606, 1984; 1988; 1991-1992; 1995; 1998 (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 36)
  - Food Service Demonstration, 1974 (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 37)
  - Ford Foundation Project at Hofstra University, 1970 (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 38)
  - Fulton Country Dinner, 1971 November 24 (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 39)
  - Genevire Clark, Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 40)
  - GHI Upstate Processing Center, 1985 December 10 (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 41)
  - Head and Shoulders (Head Shots) (1 of 9), 1970; 1984; 1989-1991; 1994-1995; Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 42)
  - Head and Shoulders (Head Shots) (2 of 9), 1970; 1984; 1989-1991; 1994-1995; Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 43)
  - Head and Shoulders (Head Shots) (3 of 9), 1970; 1984; 1989-1991; 1994-1995; Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 44)
  - Head and Shoulders (Head Shots) (4 of 9), 1970; 1984; 1989-1991; 1994-1995; Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 45)
  - Head and Shoulders (Head Shots) (5 of 9), 1970; 1984; 1989-1991; 1994-1995; Undated (Box 1 (10-Images), Folder 46)
  - Head and Shoulders (Head Shots) (6 of 9), 1970; 1984; 1989-1991; 1994-1995; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 1)
  - Head and Shoulders (Head Shots) (7 of 9), 1970; 1984; 1989-1991; 1994-1995; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 2)
  - Head and Shoulders (Head Shots) (8 of 9), 1970; 1984; 1989-1991; 1994-1995; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 3)
  - Head and Shoulders (Head Shots) (9 of 9), 1970; 1984; 1989-1991; 1994-1995; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 4)
  - Judiciary 330, 1992; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 5)
  - Labor Day, 1992 (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 6)
  - Local 881 (TOB), 1988; 1995; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 7)
  - Local 882, 1986-1987; 1991-1994; 1996-1997; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 8)
  - LIDC Local 430, 1988; 1995; 1998; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 9)
  - McDemott, Dimitry, Lennon Hauberm, Coyle, Carroll, Whitney, Carey, Fryer, Cole, Gallagher, Carr, Moore, Collins, Lathimer, Stack, Bendet,Blom/Rodgers, Dolan, Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous (1 of 3), 1971-1972; 1999; 2006; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (2 of 3), 1971-1972; 1999; 2006; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous (3 of 3), 1971-1972; 1999; 2006; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Member Photographs, 1999; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 14)
  - Nassau (1 of 3), 1979; 1983-1984; 1987-1991; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 15)
  - Nassau (2 of 3), 1979; 1983-1984; 1987-1991; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 16)
  - Nassau (3 of 3), 1979; 1983-1984; 1987-1991; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 17)
  - Negatives; Capitol Rally, Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 18)
  - Negatives; DED Employee, Rose De Sorbo, 1989; 1992 (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 19)
  - Negatives; Dutches County Infirmary, Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 20)
  - Negatives (1 of 9), 1987; 1993-1996; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 21)
  - Negatives (2 of 9), 1987; 1993-1996; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 22)
  - Negatives (3 of 9), 1987; 1993-1996; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 23)
  - Negatives (4 of 9), 1987; 1993-1996; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 24)
  - Negatives (5 of 9), 1987; 1993-1996; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 25)
  - Negatives (6 of 9), 1987; 1993-1996; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 26)
  - Negatives (7 of 9), 1987; 1993-1996; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 27)
  - Negatives (8 of 9), 1987; 1993-1996; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 28)
  - Negatives (9 of 9), 1987; 1993-1996; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 29)
  - Old Conventions (Carter), Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 30)
  - O.G.S Clambake, 1969 (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 31)
  - People DOT 609, 1982; 1990; 1992-1995; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 32)
  - People- r, 1988-1991 (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 33)
  - Photo CI (404), 1986-1989; 1991-1992; 1995; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 34)
  - Picketing against CSEA, Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 35)
  - Pilgrim 418, 1987-1988; 1990-1991; 1993 (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 36)
  - Protests (1 of 2), Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 37)
  - Protests (2 of 2), Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 38)
  - P.S.C. Hearing, 1973 December 7 (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 39)
  - Regional Elections (Statements and Photos), 1987 (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 40)
  - Regional Offices 3-6, 1984 (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 41)
  - Regional Officer Candidates, 1984 (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 42)
  - Regional Officer Elections, 1993-1996 (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 43)
  - Retirees, 1980; 1986-1988; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 44)
  - Robert R. Parks, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 45)
  - Ruth Barlies Retirement, 1970 June 26 (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 46)
  - Section 852, 1981; 1983-1985; 1987; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 47)
  - Section 852, 1981; 1983-1985; 1987; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 48)
  - Section 852, 1981; 1983-1985; 1987; Undated (Box 2 (10-Images), Folder 49)
  - Section 880, 1990; 1993; 1995; 1999; Undated (Box 3 (10-Images), Folder 1)
  - Sect-Trues AFL-CLO, 1980 (Box 3 (10-Images), Folder 2)
  - Schenectady County Department of Social Services, Undated (Box 3 (10-Images), Folder 3)
  - Slides Undated (1 of 12) (Box 3 (10-Images), Folder 4)
  - Slides Undated (2 of 12) (Box 3 (10-Images), Folder 5)
  - Slides Undated (3 of 12) (Box 3 (10-Images), Folder 6)
  - Slides Undated (4 of 12) (Box 3 (10-Images), Folder 7)
  - Slides Undated (5 of 12) (Box 3 (10-Images), Folder 8)
  - Slides Undated (6 of 12) (Box 3 (10-Images), Folder 9)
  - Slides Undated (7 or 12) (Box 3 (10-Images), Folder 10)
  - Slides Undated (8 of 12) (Box 3 (10-Images), Folder 11)
  - Slides Undated (9 of 12) (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 1)
  - Slides Undated (10 of 12) (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 2)
  - Slides Undated (11 of 12) (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 3)
  - Slides Undated (12 of 12) (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 4)
  - Speaker at White Plains, Undated (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 5)
  - Speech, Undated (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 6)
  - Staff, 1992 (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 7)
  - Stanley Horowitz, Undated (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 8)
  - State 016, 1987-1988; 1991-1993; Undated (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 9)
  - State and Local Workshop Pixs, 1990 (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 10)
  - Statewide Officer Candidate Photos, 1988 (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 11)
  - Sucow 618, 1986; 1995; Undated (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 12)
  - SUSB Local 614, 1987; 1990; 1993 (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 13)
  - Unknown, 1976 January (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 14)
  - Unknown, 1996 (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 15)
  - Welfare Reform, Undated (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 16)
  - Weschester Dinner, 1970 (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 17)
  - Where Would You Be?, Undated (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 18)
  - Workers (Scientists/Firemen), Undated (Box 4 (10-Images), Folder 19)
  - The Oneida County Chapter, Civil Service Employees..., Undated
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., Undated
  - Unidentified Civil Service Employees Association..., Undated
  - Senate Majority Leader Warren Anderson shaking..., 1980
  - The former Civil Service Employees Association..., 1982
  - New York Governor Mario Cuomo speaks at a Civil..., 1982
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Local..., 1990
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1991
  - This Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1995
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s 2001...
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2009 January
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2009 January
  - The Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1990 November
  - Master of Ceremonies Nick Paolini, president of..., 2008 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2008 November
  - Union members from the Civil Service Employees..., 2008 November
  - The Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2008 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2008 December
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2008 February
  - Retiring Civil Service Employees Association..., 2008 February
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Putnam..., 2009 February
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2008 March
  - Across New York state, Civil Service Employees..., 2009 March
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Western..., 2008 April
  - Keith Shultis, a member of the Civil Service..., 2008 April
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2008 April
  - Guild for Exceptional Children workers stand..., 2008 April
  - From left, Civil Service Employees Association..., 2009 April
  - Across New York state, Civil Service Employees..., 2009 April
  - Across New York state, Civil Service Employees..., 2009 April
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)'s..., 2008 May
  - From left, Civil Service Employees Association..., 2008 May
  - Across New York state, Civil Service Employees..., 2009 May
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2008 June
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2008 June
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2008 June
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2008 July
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2008 August
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Lansing..., 2008 August
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Auburn..., 2008 September
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2008 September
  - Delegates from Civil Service Employees Association..., 2008 September
  - A New York State Civil Service Employees..., 2002 January
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Central..., 2002 January
  - Unidentifed Civil Service Employees Association..., 2004 January
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2005 January
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2007 January
  - Van Duyn Home and Hospital Director of Safety and..., 2007 January
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) VOICE..., 2008 January
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) East..., 2008 January
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Western..., 2008 January
  - Governor David Paterson announcing Representative..., 2008 January 23
  - Unidentified Civil Service Employees Association..., 1987 October
  - A group of more than 75 unidentified Mohawk Valley..., 1991 October
  - A group of unidentified Civil Service Employees..., 1997 October
  - John Funiciello is presented with an award at the..., 2001 October
  - Three boxes of Civil Service Employees Association..., 2001 October
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2005 October
  - Niagara County, New York Local President Elaine..., 2006 October
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member,..., 2007 October
  - Drs. Michael Wilkins, left, and William Bronston..., 2007 October
  - Volunteers from the various Civil Service..., 1972 November
  - United States Congresswoman Nita Lowey speaking at..., 2002 November
  - Cathy Collette, retiring director of AFSCME's..., 2002 November
  - Former Wal-Mart executive-turned union organizer..., 2002 November
  - Schenectady Family Health Services Facility..., 2005 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2006 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2006 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 2006 November
  - The New York Drum Cafe pumping up Women's..., 2006 November
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 2006 November
  - Highway Maintenance Supervisor Jerry Bartel, left,..., 2006 November
  - Ed Collins, president of the Clarkson University..., 2006 November
  - New York State Assemblyman Ronald Canestrari..., 1999 November 23
  - Developmental Aide II Lori Nilsson, a Civil..., 2005 December
  - One of the Civil Service Employees Association..., 2005 December
  - Across the state, Civil Service Employees..., 2005 December
  - Erie County, NY Medical Center Section third Vice..., 2006 December
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 2007 December
  - A news clipping from the Utica, NY Observer-..., 1966 December 16
  - Dr. Frank L. Tolman seved as the 15th president of..., 1945-1950
  - Several hospitals at the time, notably Pilgrim..., 1949
  - Thousands of travelers passing through Grand..., 1950
  - One of Middletown's (New York) modern wards as..., 1955
  - Girls in adolescent unit at Rockland State..., 1957
  - Volunteer programs bring the community to the..., 1958
  - One of more than 167 outpatient psychiatric..., 1962
  - This Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1968
  - A postcard featuring a color drawing issued by..., 1968
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1980
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1981
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1982
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1982
  - Lori Connelly speaking at a Civil Service..., 1990
  - Larry Baker, Civil Service Employees Association..., 1990
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1990
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1990
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 1995
  - A.J. Sokojia of Civil Service Employees..., 1995
  - Clarkstown School District nurses, (standing) Joan..., 1995
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) Broome..., 1995
  - This Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1995
  - Julie Reynolds of Civil Service Employees..., 1995
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) member..., 1997
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) members..., 1998
  - Erie County retiree Vic Marr, Civil Service..., 1998
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1982 February
  - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA)..., 1982 February